Sara Pearce

312-513-8577 5717 Bolm Road, ATX

Career Highlights:

Programmer July 2017-present

XTech Staffing Austin, TX https://xtechstaffing.com

I wear many hats for the marketing and operations departments at XTech. Wordpress Webmaster, large dataset manager, digital asset designer, and automation engineer are all parts of my responsibility along with general IT and employee training with support.

Lead Developer Jan 2016-present

Left Turn Only Austin, TX http://leftturnonly.tv

With Left Turn Only, I've built a small B2B shop that focuses on white-label Wordpress development. Working in partnership with agencies and marketers, I am the owner of the website build process from design specification writing through launch and ongoing maintenance. I am completely responsible for securing hosting, testing the site, all plugins and themes, custom development of plugins or themes specific to client needs, managing build environments and workflows, project management, and client communications.

QA/Tester, Programmer and Curriculum Designer

April 2016-June 2017

Querium Corporation Austin, TX

At Querium, I tested a Virtual Math Tutor (AI Expert System) engine for clean UX functionality, mathematical accuracy and curricular alignment. My responsibilities also included managing and proofing question databases in various forms including Mathematica, JSON, and MySQL.

Full-Stack Web Developer

Social Solutions Global Austin, TX

June 2014-Dec 2015

At Social Solutions, I executed product features and site maintenance to the specifications of the product and development teams focused on Domain Driven Design. As a part of the development team, I contributed to planning, coding, and peer support of new features. By the end of my time, I had been the primary developer on 8 new product features.

HIGH PROFICIENCIES:

- * PHP/Wordpress
- * JS/jQuery
- * CSS/Bootstrap
- * HTML5
- * Git
- * Vagrant/VVV

MODERATE PROFICIENCIES:

- * Angular
- * Bourbon/Neat
- * Vue.is
- * Mathematica
- * Pvthon
- * d3
- * Grunt
- * Photoshop

MODERATE PROFICIENCIES:

- * JS/Mootools
- * PHP/Zend/Smarty
- * Compass
- * AWS/Lambda
- * SVN
- * Balsamia

URLS:

Personal: http://sarapearce.net Business: http://leftturnonly.tv

Education:

University of Minnesota: BA Mathematics University of Minnesota: M.Ed Math Education